1	1	Tesla	Tesla	NNP	ORGANIZATION
1	2	Motors	Motors	NNPS	ORGANIZATION
1	3	Inc	Inc	NNP	ORGANIZATION
1	4	is	be	VBZ	O
1	5	partnered	partner	VBN	O
1	6	with	with	IN	O
1	7	Serendio	Serendio	NNP	ORGANIZATION
1	8	Inc	Inc	NNP	ORGANIZATION
1	9	,	,	,	O
1	10	Santa	Santa	NNP	LOCATION
1	11	Clara	Clara	NNP	LOCATION
1	12	.	.	.	O


